DAVID CLEMEN: Hi.
Alright, now that I've plopped my white paint, I'm going to pick up my favorite tool again.
And I'm just going to come in here and just kinda fill it out.
And now, when you mix the red and white in big areas, if it's too much red and you don't move it fast enough, you'll start to get pink so I want to try and keep the integrity of the white and I'm just going to move that fast, and see how--I don't know if you can see it, but since the paint has kind of dried quickly on this paint on the wood, it's already created a texture underneath of it.
So, now, I'm getting this texture of the paint underneath of it.
So, I'm just going to come in here and do these big squeegee marks and not going to go too crazy with it.
And I'm not trying to cover up all the red.
I'm just trying to get certain areas and show the white on the top of the red.
And then, I can come in and I can actually just do almost like, I guess you would say it's like almost a karate chop or samurai swing to the right or left.
I'm left-handed but I played sports with right, so I do squeegee with the right hand.
And so, that's squeegeeing the second color.